你离开了
You left.
你哥哥和我 我们需要你
Your brother and me … we needed you.
你却这么走了 萨姆
You walked away, Sam.
你就这么走了
You walked away!
爸爸是你说过不要再回来了
You're the one who said "don't come back, " Dad.
是你关上了门而不是我
You're the one who closed that door, not me!
萨姆 我只是不能接受这个事实
Sammy, I just couldn't accept the fact.
你和我 截然不同
That you and me … we're just different.
我们不再截然不同了 不再会了
We're not different. not anymore.
露比 我已经好几个星期没有喝血了 我需要它
Ruby, it's been weeks. I need it.
你知道你跨出底线多远了吗
Do you even know how far off the reservation you've gone?
脱离正常 脱离人性多远了吗
How far from normal? from human?
你弟弟正走上一条不归路 迪恩
Your brother is headed down a dangerous road, Dean.
萨姆 你做得真得是太离谱了
It's already gone too far, Sam.
如果我不认识你
If I didn't know you,
我一定会杀了你
I would want to hunt you.
不
No!
滚开 不
Go away! no!
我的上帝啊
Oh, my god.
上帝啊 主啊
Oh, god. oh, lord.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
上帝啊 上帝啊
Oh, god. oh, god.
好吧 上帝 没事 一切安好
Okay. god. it's okay. it's okay.
不
No! aah!
救命
Help! aah!
不
No!
上帝啊
Oh! god!
[邪恶力量 第4季第19集]
睡得好吗
How'd you sleep?
你说呢
How do you think?
饿死了 去吃早饭吧
I'm starving. let's get breakfast.
去哪吃 两个小时的车程内似乎什么也没有
Where? we're like two hours from anything.
但我真是饿得不行了
But I'm hungry now.
后座上还有一个三明治
There's probably a sandwich in the backseat still.
金枪鱼味
It's tuna.
那不是老爸的手机吗
Isn't that Dad's phone?
喂
hello?
是约翰吗
Um, is … is this John?
他没办法接电话 有什么我能帮你的吗
He can't come to the phone. can I help you?
不 我得和约翰本人谈谈
No, no… I really need to talk to John.
我是亚当·密里根 他认识我
This is Adam Milligan. he knows me.
很遗憾告诉你这个坏消息 哥们儿
Well, sorry to be the one to break this to you, pal,
但约翰2年前就死了
But John died more than two years ago.
你是谁
Who is this?
我是他儿子
I'm his son.
温德姆 明尼苏达州
迪恩 听我说 亚当·密里根确有其人
Dean, look, best I can tell, Adam Milligan is real.
生于1990年9月29日 母亲是凯特·密里根
Born september 29, 1990, to Kate Milligan.
出生证明上父亲一栏是空的
No father listed on the birth certificate.
他是个鹰级童子军
He's an eagle scout.
高中毕业时满载着各种荣誉
Graduated from high school with honors.
现在就读于威斯康辛大学
And currently goes to the university of Wisconsin.
生物专业 医学预科
Biology major, pre-med.
迪恩 你在听吗
Dean? you listening?
绝对是个陷阱
This is a trap.
迪恩 跟你说了 这小子身份属实
Dean, I'm telling you … the kid checks out.
好极了 所以他是地球上的大活人一个
Great, so he's an actual person on the planet earth.
不幸的是他被恶魔附了身
Sucks he's got a demon in him.
你好 欢迎光临「奥利佛表哥茶餐厅」
Hi. welcome to cousin oliver's.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 请问 - 我们其实是来等人的
- Can I… - we're actually waiting on somebody.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在搞什么
What are you …
圣水吗
Holy water?
是的 只需来一口耶稣果汁
Yep … one sip of jesus juice,
那该死的恶魔就会痛不欲生了
This evil bitch is gonna be in a world of hurt.
如果他没被附身呢
And what if he's not possessed?
那他就是个变形怪
Then he is a shapeshifter.
所以连银器都备好了
Hence the silver.
总之那家伙是要付出代价的
Look, either way, this thing is gonna bleed.
竟然用老爸做诱饵
I mean, using Dad as bait?
这是他犯得最致命错误 可怜虫
That's the last mistake of its short, pitiful life.
怎么啦
What?
迪恩
Dean…
听着 老爸的日记上有这么一条
Listen … there's an entry in dad's journal.
在1990年1月
From january of 1990.
上面记载他去明尼苏达调查
Saying he's headed to minnesota to check out a case.
粗算一下时间 嗯
That's, roughly, oh,
正好是那小子出生前9个月
About nine months before the kid was born.
- 巧合罢了 - 巧合吗
- Coincidence. - coincidence?
接下来的两页日记
Next two pages of the journal.
被扯掉了
Torn out.
你不是真相信老爸多了个儿子吧
You're not actually buying this, are you?
听着老哥 我也不想相信这些
Look, man, I don't want to believe it, either.
我只是说这有可能
I'm just saying it's possible.
老爸每次外出都是几个星期之久
I mean, Dad would be gone for weeks at a time,
他又不是吃素的
And he wasn't exactly a monk.
一个猎鬼者孤身来到了小镇
I mean, a hunter rolls into town,
消灭了怪物 又拯救了美女
Uh, kills a monster, saves the girl…
有时姑娘会以身相许来报君恩
Sometimes the girl's grateful.
你害我开始YY老爸XXOO的场面了
Well, now I'm thinking about dad sex.
别再说了
Stop talking.
也许他就只是一次没克制住
Maybe he slipped one past the goalie.
哥们儿
dude!
亚当
Adam?
你是萨姆
You Sam?
是的 这是迪恩
Yeah. uh, this is Dean.
你们怎么认识我老爸的
How'd you know my Dad?
我们一起工作过
We worked together.
他是怎么死的
How did he die?
因公殉职
On the job.
他不是个修理工吗
He was a mechanic, right?
被车压了
A car fell on him.
亚当 你好吗
Hey, Adam. How you doing?
我要喝这杯水
Oh, I'll take that.
真是渴死了
I am very thirsty.
还是老样子吗 亚当
The usual, Adam?
是啊 谢谢关心 丹妮斯
Uh, yeah. Thanks, Denise.
你最后一次见约翰是什么时候
So, when's the last time you saw John?
我也不记得了 几年前吧
I don't even know. it's…a couple years.
为什么现在才打电话给他呢
Why did you decide to call him now?
我不知道还能打给谁
I didn't know who else to call.
他是我仅有的亲人了
He's the only family I got.
我妈妈失踪了
My mom's missing.
是吗 真遗憾 有多久了
Really? I'm sorry. uh, for how long?
太悲惨了 真的
It's tragic, really.
但如果你真是约翰的儿子
But if you're John's kid,
我们怎么从来没听说过
How could we've never heard of you?
因为他和我原先并不知道对方的存在
'cause John and me didn't really know each other.
几年前才知道的
Not until a few years ago, anyway.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我妈妈从未对我提过他
My mom never talked about him.
我对他知之甚少
I knew some stuff.
你都知道些什么
What kind of stuff?
我妈是个护士
My mom's a nurse,
有次爸爸伤的很重 进了急诊室
And dad came into the E.R. pretty torn up.
大概是由于打猎事故之类的
Hunting accident or something.
我还知道他的名字 约翰·温彻斯特
And I knew his name John Winchester.
就这些了
That's about it.
我们不能算是个三口家庭
We're not exactly a nuclear family.
是啊 现在谁的家庭又是完整的呢
Yeah, well, who is these days?
你第一次见到他 是在什么时候呢
So, when did you, uh, when did you finally meet him?
12岁的时候吧
When I was 12.
我妈一直留着他以前的电话号码
My mom had one of his old numbers.
我一直求她 不停地求
And after I begged her … god, 24/7 …
她才终于打给了他
She finally called him.
老天 约翰一听说我的存在
God, when John heard he had a son,
立马飞奔到这儿
He raced to town.
他放下了所有的事情
I mean, he dropped everything.
连夜开车赶来
He drove all night.
- 请慢用 - 谢谢
- There you go. - Thanks.
听起来真是窝心啊
Well, that's heartwarming.
不介意我吃点东西吧
You mind?
当然 客气啥 吃吧
No, please … dig in.
之后他大概一年左右来一次
He would swing by once a year or so,
时不时还会打来电话
You know, called when he could.
不过还是
But still…
他教我玩扑克 打台球
He taught me poker and pool.
还在我15岁时给我买了第一杯啤酒
And even bought me my first beer when I was 15.
他教我开车
He showed me how to drive.
爸爸 他有辆迷人的67年黑羚羊
Dad … he had this beautiful '67 Impala.
瞎扯
Oh, this is crap.
你在说谎
You know what … you're lying.
- 不 我没说谎 - 才怪 你就在说谎
- No, I'm not. - uh, yeah, you are.
抱歉 但你凭什么说我在说谎
I'm sorry, but who the hell are you to call me a liar?
我们才是是约翰·温彻斯特的儿子 货真价实的
We're John Winchester's sons, that's true.
我们才是他的儿子
We are his sons.
也就是说我还有哥哥
I've got brothers?
不 谁说是你哥哥了
No, you don't have brothers.
听着 伙计 我可不管你是不是猎人
Look, man, I don't know if you're a hunter.
还是想玩什么把戏
Or what kind of game you're playing here.
我从没打过猎
I have never been hunting in my life.
随便吧 我要走了 我们闪 萨姆
Whatever. I'm out of here. Come on, Sam.
我可以证明
I can prove it.
他带你去看棒球比赛了
He took you to a baseball game?
是啊 我14岁的时候
Yeah, when I turned 14.
爸爸陪我过了几个生日
Dad was around for a few of my birthdays.
2004年9月29日
September 29, 2004.
就一个词 明尼苏达
One word … "Minnesota."
他真带你去看他娘的棒球比赛了
He took you to a freakin' baseball game?
是的
Yeah.
怎么 你过生日时老爸带你去干嘛
Why? what'd Dad do with you on your birthday?
亚当 你说你打电话给老爸
Adam, you said you called dad.
是因为你妈失踪了
Because your mom was missing.
对
Yeah.
她失踪多久了
How long has she been gone?
三天了
Three days.
最后一个见她的人是谁
Who was the last person to see her?
安比南帝先生 我们的邻居
Mr. Abbinanti, our neighbor.
他周二晚上看到她回家了
He saw her come home tuesday night,
但她周三就没去上班
But she never showed up to work on wednesday.
你报警了吗
Did you call the police?
妈妈医院的上司报了警
Mom's supervisor at the hospital did.
我也就尽快赶过来了
And then I drove down here as fast as I could.
我本应该在这儿的
I should have been here.
那 警察是怎么说
What'd the, uh, what'd the cops say?
他们检查了屋子
That they, uh, they searched the house.
但没任何发现
They didn't find anything.
她绝不会一声不响就离开的
She wouldn't leave without telling anybody.
她就像是人间蒸发了一样
It's like she just dropped off the face of the earth,
明白吗
You know?
除了床头柜被撞翻了
The, uh, nightstand was knocked over.
还有其他发现吗
Was there anything else?
没有
Oh, not really.
警长说没有外人闯入的迹象
The sheriff said there's no sign of a break-in.
怎么 你认为警察们遗漏了什么吗
What, you think the cops missed something?
可能吧
Maybe.
他们眼力可不如我
They don't have my eyes.
你不就是个修理工吗
You're a mechanic.
是啊 没错
Yeah. That's right.
迪恩 能跟我说些老爸的其他事儿吗
Dean, what else can you tell me about Dad?
你很了解他了
You knew him.
但远不及你们
Not as well as you.
相信我 小鬼 保有点神秘好些
Trust me, kid. You don't want to know.
失陪一下
Give us a minute.
跟警察聊过了吗
You talk to the cops?
对 如亚当所说 没任何线索
Yeah. like Adam said, no leads on his mom.
意料之中
Shocker there.
可是我找到这个
But I did find this.
瞧这个
Here.
在1990年 温德姆这儿发生过17起盗墓案
In 1990, there were 17 grave robberies in windom.
这就是老爸会来这里的原因
That's why dad came through here?
我想是的
I'd say so.
看看这里
Check it out.
好极了 这么说他是来猎捕的 但是什么呢
All right, so he was hunting something. what?
毫无头绪
No idea.
那几页日记全都被他撕下来了
Those were the pages he tore out of the journal.
但上个月 盗尸案又再度发生
But last month, the corpse-snatching started up again.
在本地公墓里有三具尸体被盗
Three bodies from the local cemetery.
不管他猎得是什么 都没能斩草除根
So whatever he was after, he didn't kill it.
那东西又回来了
It's back.
而且 还更是变本加厉开始爱吃鲜肉了
And…what … it's stepped up its game to fresh meat?
不仅是凯特失踪 还有
I mean, Kate's missing, and, uh…
当地的一名酒保 叫乔·巴顿
So is a local bartender … a guy named Joe Barton.
你妈妈认识乔·巴顿吗
Hey, does your mom know Joe Barton?
不认识吧 怎么了
I don't think so. why?
怎么了
What is it?
小心
Watch out.
帮我把这个床垫移走
Give me a hand with the mattress.
每次都输
Every time.
我干嘛就没出布呢
Why didn't I throw paper?
（欢迎来到Soony Buana Lounge享受欢乐时光）
你们到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
亚当 冷静点
Adam, hey. take it easy.
别叫我冷静 行吗
No, don't tell me to take it easy, okay?
我家成了犯罪现场
My house is a crime scene,
我妈妈很可能已经死了
My mom's probably dead.
而你们两
And you two.
支我去报了警
Well, you tell me to call the cops.
自己却在他们来之前闪了
But you got to bail before they show?
你们到底是谁
So, who are you really?
警察对我妈妈的去向毫无头绪
Cops didn't know where to look for my mom.
但你却有本事查清 迪恩
Dean, but you did.
而之前我听到你们提到了
And I heard you talking earlier.
什么盗墓者
Something about grave robberies.
你们并不是修理工
You're not mechanics.
我只想弄明白究竟发生了什么事
I just want to know what's going on.
求你们了
Please.
我们是猎鬼者
We're hunters.
萨姆
Sammy!
他应该知道的 迪恩
He deserves to know, Dean.
你所谓的猎人是猎什么的
What do you mean, "hunters"?
好吧 你的意思是
Okay, so… basically,
电影里面的那些个怪兽
You're saying that every movie monster,
还有我以前所做的噩梦
Every nightmare that I've ever had.
其实都是真的
That's all real?
但哥斯拉绝对是假的
"godzilla's" just a movie.
我们就是猎杀它们
We hunt them.
老爸也是
So did Dad.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 就这么个反应
"Okay"? That's it?
我还能说什么
What am I supposed to say?
说我们瞎掰 或是神经病的大有人在
That we're liars, that we're crazy.
就是没人会说 好吧
Nobody just says "okay."
你们可是我的哥哥
You're my brothers.
你们没必要骗我 不是吗
You're telling me the truth, right?
- 当然 - 那我相信你们
- Yeah. - then I believe you.
那抓走我妈妈的是什么
What took my mom?
我们还不确定
We're not sure.
目前只知道有东西在镇上偷肉体
Something's in town stealing bodies.
而且是不论死活
Living and dead.
置于具体是什么还不得而知
But we don't know what.
有很多怪胎都符合这些个特征
There's a long list of freaks that fit the bill.
你们觉得她还可能活着吗
You think maybe she might still be alive?
- 我能帮些什么吗 - 不必了
- How can I help? - you can't.
那东西杀了我妈妈
This thing killed my mom.
我希望能加入你们 手刃它
If you're hunting it, I want in.
没门儿
No.
- 迪恩 也许 - 也许什么
- Dean, look, maybe - maybe what?
他失去了妈妈
He lost his mother.
我们应该能够体会他的感受
Maybe we can understand what that feels like.
你觉得为什么老爸从没跟我们提起他呢
Why do you think dad never told us about this kid, sam?
又为什么要撕掉这几页呢
Why do you think he ripped out the pages?
- 因为 - 因为他想保护他
- Because - because he was protecting him!
爸爸死了 迪恩
Dad's dead, Dean.
那又怎样
That doesn't matter!
他不想让亚当过着跟我们一样的生活
He didn't want Adam to have our lives, okay?
所以我们得尊重他的遗愿
And we're gonna respect his wishes.
我能插句话吗
Do I get a say in this?
- 不行 - 不行
- No! - no.
看好这孩子
Babysit the kid.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
出去透个气
I'm going out!
他都是这样子吗
Is he always like that?
欢迎加入我们的大家庭
Welcome to the family.
给
Here.
我要教你一些东西
I'm gonna teach you a few things.
但迪恩不是说
Dean said.
我知道迪恩说了什么
I know what Dean said.
但我更清楚报仇雪恨的滋味
And I know what it's like to want revenge.
这座坟墓建于1926年
This tomb was built in 1926.
米尔萨普家的四代人都安葬于此
Four generations of the Millsap family were interred here.
我以后绝不会这样安葬自己
I don't build mausoleum anymore.
那纽金特探员 你好好考虑过
Tell me, agent Nugent, have you thought about.
自己以后根归何处了吗
Where you might like to spend eternity?
他妈的天天都在想
All the damn time.
失踪了三具尸体
So, three bodies went missing.
有嫌疑人吗
Any idea who did it?
流氓吧 而且还是变态又神经的流氓
Hooligans … sick, deranged hooligans.
这不是血 是什么
This isn't blood. what is this?
那是防腐剂
No, it's embalming fluid.
盗尸者不但搬走了尸体
Whoever committed this crime didn't just take the corpses.
还将他们开膛破肚
They opened them up.
到这儿的警察 头杯啤酒都免费
First beer's on the house for cops.
联邦警探也不例外
Feds, too.
我这么容易被认出来吗
Am I that obvious?
本地的警察我都认识
I know all the local badges,
但你有《法律与秩序》里那种探员的气质
And you've got that "law & order" vibe.
联邦调查局来温德姆调查什么呢
So, what's the fbi doing in windom?
我正在调查乔·巴顿的失踪案
I'm looking into the disappearance of Joe Barton.
看来你认识他啊
I assume you knew him?
不只认识
A little.
我是他的妻子
I'm his wife.
我叫丽莎
Lisa.
丽莎 能跟我说下他失踪的事情吗
Well, Lisa, what can you tell me about his disappearance?
该讲的我都跟警长说过了
Same thing I told the sheriff.
他上周五晚上一直在店里盘货
He stayed late friday before last to do inventory.
就再也没回家
Never came home.
警察怎么说
And the police?
什么都没说
Nothing.
说实话 我很担心他们会放弃找他
Truth is, I was scared they stopped looking.
幸好你来了
But now you're here.
乔也是警察吗
Joe was a cop?
还是副警长
Deputy.
不过在任时间不长
For a little while.
不过是很久以前的事了
That was a long time ago.
他在职期间有参与调查过 嗯
He didn't happen to work the, uh, the … the …
90年代的盗墓案吗
The grave-robbery case back in '90?
他有参与
He did. yeah.
就是乔找到那些尸体的
Joe was the one who found those bodies.
还因此获得了嘉奖
He got an award for that.
那可是件有趣的案子
That was an interesting case.
数名失踪者的尸体已找到
17具尸体在荒废已久的屋中找到
他跟你说过他是怎么找到的吗
He ever tell you how he did it?
大部分时间
Most of the time,
他都会自夸全靠自己警察的自觉
He said good, solid police work.
但在醉醺醺的时候
But after a few beers,
他又会承认是因为有人帮忙
He'd admit he had a little help.
是谁
From who?
一个专家 他是这么说的
A "specialist" … that's all he'd say.
警察有抓到那个偷尸体的人吗
Cops ever find the guy that stole the bodies?
没有
No.
不过我问起乔时
But when I asked joe about it.
他总说别再担心了
He'd say not to worried.
我们都办妥了
That "we took care of what done it."
萨姆
Sam…
爸爸到底是怎么死的
How did dad really die?
被恶魔杀死的
Demon.
那你杀了那恶魔没
You hunted it down?
替老爸报仇雪恨了吗
Got revenge?
迪恩亲手结果了它
Dean killed it.
那么算是结束了吧
So it's over for you.
这事永无止境
It's never over.
出什么事了
What the …
呆在这
Stay here.
在通风口里
It's in the vents.
快走
Go!
快跑
你的车呢
Where's your car?
停在那里
Over here.
快 钥匙拿来
Come on. Keys.
给
Here.
萨姆
Sam!
迪恩 快帮忙
Dean, help!
我打中那东西了
I winged it.
你看清是什么了吗
Did you see anything?
根本无暇看清
I didn't get a good look.
到底是什么鬼东西啊
What the hell is this thing?
我们要去追吗
Should we go after it?
不 不用
No, no.
那迷宫样地方 恐怕早跑得无影无踪了
In that maze? that thing's long gone.
好吧 虽然还不清楚那是什么
All right, so, we don't know what it is,
但至少知道了他的目标
But we do know who it's going after.
先是乔·巴顿 亚当的妈妈
Joe Barton, Adam's mom.
接着就是亚当了
And Adam.
专门躲在车底 守株待兔
It was under his truck, just waiting for him.
我竟直直地走入了它设下的陷阱里
It set a trap, and I walked right into it.
别介怀了
Doesn't matter.
你分析地没错 这是有针对性的
You're right, there's a pattern.
乔·巴顿曾是个警察
Joe Barton was a cop.
我很肯定他帮过老爸
I'm pretty sure he helped out Dad.
目前我们找到他 老爸的女人
So we've got him, Dad's girl…
还有他的儿子
And his son.
全是老爸在这儿的旧识
All the people Dad knew in town.
至少我们知道了它回来的原因
At least we know why it's back.
它是来复仇的
It wants revenge.
快去收拾你的东西 我们得赶紧离开
Grab your stuff. we'll hit the road.
我们不该就这么离开
We shouldn't leave.
是啊 呆在这儿
Yeah, let's stay here,
呆在老爸和小鬼她妈调情的房子里
Where the kid's mom got ganked.
真是个好主意
Good one.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
不 萨姆 我们得先带这孩子离开
No, Sam, we're gonna take the kid,
把他交给鲍比后
We're gonna drop him off at Bobby's,
我和你再回来
And then you and me are gonna come back here.
解决老爸结下的梁子
And finish what dad started.
要怎么解决
How?
没线索 没证人
We got no leads, no witnesses.
唯一有的就是那东西的目标
We do have what this thing wants.
你想让那孩子作诱饵
You want to use the kid as bait?
所以才一直坚持要他留下是吗
That's why you want to stay here?
或许那东西还会回来
Maybe this thing will come back.
我们可以教教亚当 让他有所准备
We could train Adam … get him ready.
他随时会送命的 萨姆
He could die, Sam.
我们也随时会没命 迪恩
We could all die, Dean.
就算我们这次能杀了这个
Even if we do kill this thing,
但要找爸爸和我们报仇的恶魔
There are tons of other freaks that want revenge.
还会层出不穷的
On dad, on us.
如果再找上了那孩子 他还是毫无准备怎么办
What if they find the kid instead and he's not ready?
我愿意
I'll do it.
我愿意学 不管付出何种代价
Whatever it takes, I'll do it.
我想学
I want to do it.
私人财产禁止进入
违者将依照明尼苏达州的刑法接受严厉制裁
很容易的
It's easy.
只要将后作力和开枪的时机配合好
Just feel the recoil and time the trigger pulls.
你来开三枪
Three taps.
真得吗
Yeah?
来试试吧
Go ahead.
看来新手运气真挺好 是不
Beginner's luck, right?
不 老弟 你很有天赋
Nah, man. you're a natural.
射得漂亮
Good shooting.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
地狱之犬
怨灵
所以 之后我们用火烧了它
So, then we lit it on fire.
是用自制的喷火器吗
With a homemade flamethrower?
是的 很容易做
Yeah. they're easy to build.
我会教你的
I'll show you.
你们真得很在行啊 伙计
That is some job you got, man.
当猎鬼者可不是工作 亚当
Being a hunter isn't a job, Adam.
而是生活
It's life.
你是医学院预科生
You're pre-med.
一定有女朋友和朋友对吗
You got a girlfriend, friends?
以后不会再有了
Not anymore you don't.
如果你真打算踏出这一步
If you're really gonna do this,
就必须抛下所有的牵绊
You can't have those kinds of connections.
永远地抛下
Ever.
因为他们只会是你的软肋
They're weaknesses.
而你也只会将他们置于险境中
You'll just put those people in danger.
给他们带去杀身之祸
Get them killed.
那是我们必须牺牲的
That's the price we pay.
而一旦抛下 就再没回头路了
You cut them out, and you don't look back.
之后你唯一可以信任依靠的
There's only one thing you can count on.
就只有家人了
Family.
萨姆
Sam.
过来聊几句
Can I talk to you?
该死的你到底在干嘛
What the hell was that?
怎么啦
What?
那句 猎鬼就是生活 你必须抛下一切
"Hunting is life. you can't have connections."
不正是老爸曾对你说的话吗
Dad gave you that exact same speech, remember?
就在你离开我们去斯坦福之前说的
It was just before you ditched us for Stanford.
你曾那么厌烦老爸说得那些话
You hated Dad for saying that stuff,
而如今你却原封不动地引述给他
And now you're quoting him?
是的 我只是意识到老爸是对的
Yeah, well… turns out Dad was right.
几时的事儿
Since when?
一直以来都是
Since always.
迪恩 看到亚当时 知道我在想什么吗
Dean, when I look at Adam, you know what I see?
一个正常长大的孩子
A normal kid.
不 是美味的肥肉
No. meat.
因为在那些恶魔和怪物眼中
Because to the demons and monsters out there,
他就是块美味的肥肉
That's all he is.
曾经我一度很恨老爸 很恨
I hated Dad for a long time. I did.
但如今我想通了
But now I think I understand.
虽然我们不曾过过一天正常人的生活
So we didn't have a dog and a white picket fence.
那又怎样 至少老爸为了我们好
So what? Dad did right by us.
至少他让我们有了自保的能力
He taught us how to protect ourselves.
亚当也应掌握同样的能力
Adam deserves the same.
你说得这是什么话 老弟
Listen to yourself, man.
我说错了吗
You think I'm wrong?
我知道我们是没得选了
I think it's too late for us.
这就是我们的生活 我们的人生
This is our life. this is who we are, okay?
没什么可抱怨的 我完全接受了
And it's fine. I accept that.
但对于亚当而言
But with Adam.
他还有得选 老弟
He's still got a chance, man.
他还有机会去上学 有机会成为一名医生
He can go to school. he could be a doctor.
为什么亚当就可以选择
What makes Adam so special?
- 干嘛 你是在嫉妒这孩子吗 - 你不吗
- What, are you jealous of the kid? - are you?
迪恩
Dean…
这一切
All this…
都不是真的
It's not real.
亚当所了解的那个老爸 不是真实的
The Dad Adam knew … he wasn't real.
那些隐藏在黑暗深处的东西 才是真实的
The things out there in the shadows … they are real.
这个世界岌岌可危 那才是真实的
The world is coming to an end. that's real.
说什么度过美好的一天
Everything else is just part of the crap.
根本就是阿Q式地自欺欺人
People tell themselves to get through the day.
老爸没给我们选择的机会 就算了
Dad didn't have a choice with us, okay?
但亚当 他有选择的权利
But with Adam, he did.
亚当不必承受这份诅咒
Adam doesn't have to be cursed.
他也是温切斯特家的一员
He's a winchester.
显然已经遭受诅咒了
He's already cursed.
不
No.
不 不管猎捕亚当的是什么
No, whatever's hunting Adam.
我一定会查个水落石出
I'm gonna find it.
你已经查了个底朝天了 迪恩
You already looked everywhere, Dean.
那么 我就再去查一次
Well, then I'll look again.
家 多温馨的家啊
Home sweet home.
可怜的乔
sloppy Joe.
混蛋
Oh, son of a bitch!
真他妈的混蛋
Son of a bitch.
好了
All right.
所有进屋的路都封死了
We've closed off every other way into the house.
唯一能进来的通道
If this thing's coming,
就只剩这条路了
It's coming through here.
你不是说
You were saying?
亚当
Adam!
- 妈妈 - 别去
- Mom? - no.
- 妈妈 - 亚当
- Mom! - Adam!
妈妈
Mom.
亚当 等一下
Adam, wait!
虽然被抓走了 但我还是逃了出来
It took me, but I got away.
我逃出来了
I got away.
亚当 离她远点儿
Adam, step away from her.
萨姆 怎么了
Sam, what the hell?!
她不是你妈妈
She's not your mother!
亚当 这是谁 怎么回事儿
Adam, who … what is going on?
- 离他远点儿 - 这是怎么回事儿
- Get away from him! - what is going on?
- 听我的 - 真的是她 真的
- You listen to me. - it's really her, okay?
流了那么多血 你母亲绝不可能活着
There was too much blood. your mother's dead.
通风口里有那么多血迹
There was too much blood in the vents!
亚当
Adam!
开枪啊
Shoot it!
他疯了 宝贝 是我啊
He's crazy! Honey, it's me!
听着亚当 真的是我
Look … Adam! it's me!
它绝不是你妈妈
That's not your mother!
开枪 它不是人类
Shoot it! it's not human!
我知道
I know.
银器
Silver.
难怪所有测试都不起作用
No wonder none of the tests worked.
你们根本就不是易形者
You're not shapeshifters.
而是食尸鬼
You're ghouls.
我觉得这个词有很强的种族歧视
You know, I find that term racist.
新鲜人肉 比之前那些好太多了
Fresh meat. so much better than what we're used to.
我早该想到的
I should have known.
但是猎杀活人迷惑了我
It was the fresh kills that threw me.
食尸鬼通常不会找活人
Ghouls don't usually go after the living.
因为 你们只是下流的食腐动物
See, you're just filthy scavengers,
以死人为食
Feeding off the dead.
再化身成你们吃下的死者
Taking the form of the last corpse you choke down.
并吸取了他们的想法和记忆
And their thoughts. and their memories.
譬如化身成亚当
Like Adam, for instance.
我们吃什么就是什么
Well, we are what we eat.
就是两只怪物
You're monsters.
萨姆 这个词你倒是经常用
You know, you use that word a lot, sam.
但你未必真正了解其涵义
But I don't think you know what it means.
他的血 有点儿不太一样
His blood … it tastes different.
我们的父亲就是怪物
Our father was a monster?
凭什么这么说 就凭他所吃的东西吗
Why? because of what he ate?
他从未伤害过任何人啊 萨姆
He never hurt anyone, sam.
至少 没伤过活人
Living, anyway.
是的
No.
他绝不是什么怪物
He was no monster.
但是杀他的那个人就绝对是
But the thing that killed him was.
一个叫约翰·温彻斯特的怪物
A monster named John Winchester.
这够呛的
Holy crap.
多亏了你老爸
Thanks to your daddy,
我们姐弟俩不得不自力更生
My brother and I grew up on our own.
让我们相依为命
At least we had each other.
就像你和你老哥那样
Like you and your brother.
相濡以沫
Inseparable.
实际上 想把你们各个击破还真不容易
Actually, it was very hard to get you on your own.
正如你所说 萨姆
Like you said, Sam,
你唯一能指望的就是家人了
The only thing you can count on is family.
二十年来 我们活得像老鼠
And for 20 years, we lived like rats.
一个又一个的坟地
Graveyard after graveyard,
全都是发臭的肉
All that stinking flesh.
突然我们想到了
Then we thought,
干嘛不去试点新鲜的呢
"Hey, why not move up to fresher game?"
而自然也想到了下手的好地方
And we knew just where to start.
复仇 是永无止境 不是吗 萨姆
Revenge … it's never over, is it, Sam?
首先 就从约翰那警察朋友下手
First, it was john's cop friend,
然后就是他的女人 和他的儿子
And then his slut, and then his son.
接着我立马打给了约翰 但
Then I called john, but…
他个该死的竟然已经挂了
The son of a bitch was already dead.
所以只好让你和迪恩父债子偿了
So I guess you and dean will have to do instead.
这一次半路不会再杀出个迪恩来了
Dean won't interrupt us this time.
我们可以尽情尽兴地享用你
We're gonna feed on you nice and slow.
就像享用亚当那样
Like we did with Adam.
噢 顺便告诉你
Oh, and, by the way,
他确实是你们的小弟弟
He really was your brother.
你有权知道这个事实
You should know that.
我们咬第一口的时候他还有口气
He was still alive when we took our first bites.
他可真会尖叫
And he was a screamer.
萨姆 你越是挣扎
Sam, the more you struggle,
血就流得越快
The faster you're gonna bleed out.
所以还是好好躺着 放轻松
So you might as well lie back and relax.
迪恩 他们是食尸鬼
Dean, they're ghouls!
也就是说得爆头
Which means head-shot.
迪恩
Dean!
起来 坐起来 坐起来
Come on. come on. come on.
别动 别动
Hang on. hang on.
好了 我来
All right, here we go.
我来
Here we go.
坚持住 伙计
Hang on, buddy.
没事了 没事了
All right. all right.
谢了
Thank you.
这不正是家人该做的吗
That's what family's for, right?
再压一会儿
Keep pressure on that.
确定要这么做吗
You sure we should do this?
食尸鬼没捏造那些照片
Ghouls didn't fake those pictures.
更不会捏造老爸的日志
They didn't fake dad's journal.
亚当确实是我们的弟弟
Adam was our brother.
他死得像猎鬼者
He died like a hunter.
那就该有个猎鬼者的葬礼
He deserves to go out like one.
或许我们可以让他起死回生
Maybe we can bring him back…
找卡西 让他帮个忙
Get ahold of cass, call in a favor.
不 亚当已经荣登极乐了
No, Adam's in a better place.
知道吗 我终于明白了
You know, I finally get.
为什么你和老爸会经常斗气了
Why you and Dad butted heads so much.
你俩简直就是一个模子刻出来的
You two were practically the same person.
我有多崇拜他 你很清楚
I mean, I worshipped the guy, you know?
不止在穿衣打扮和行为举止 模仿他
I-I dressed like him, I acted like him,
甚至还听一样的音乐
I listen to the same music.
但你永远都比我更像他
But you were more like him than I will ever be.
到现在才明白
And I see that now.
我把这话当是赞美了
I'll take that as a compliment.
随你吧
You take it any way you want.